http://www.dolcetours.com/privacy-policy

Reservations
Wine Tours/Land of BaroloXtreme PiedmontSlow Food FestaTrufflemaniaAmarone & the AlpsTuscan Wine TreasuresXtreme TuscanyUtterly UmbriaAmalfi Coast for Wine LoversDiscover SicilyThe Volcanic Wines of EtnaRioja RoundupThe Douro ValleyDay Tours
Active Tours/Piedmont & Cinque Terre TrailsAlps & DolomitesTuscan TrekAmalfi Coast HikeSicilian SaunterPedal PiedmontChianti by Bike
Calendar/
About/What Clients SayContact UsE-News
Living La Dolce Vita blog/
Newsletter/
Reservations/
Wine tours in Italy, Spain & Portugal
Privacy Policy
Wine Tours/Land of BaroloXtreme PiedmontSlow Food FestaTrufflemaniaAmarone & the AlpsTuscan Wine TreasuresXtreme TuscanyUtterly UmbriaAmalfi Coast for Wine LoversDiscover SicilyThe Volcanic Wines of EtnaRioja RoundupThe Douro ValleyDay Tours
Active Tours/Piedmont & Cinque Terre TrailsAlps & DolomitesTuscan TrekAmalfi Coast HikeSicilian SaunterPedal PiedmontChianti by Bike
Calendar/
About/What Clients SayContact UsE-News
Living La Dolce Vita blog/
Newsletter/
Reservations/
Our privacy policy at La Dolce Vita Wine Tours is quite simple. We will not share, sell, give away, or trade any of your personal information to any third party. All the information given to us—whether on the Reservation form or in the Newsletter sign-up form—is used only by us.Your phone number will be used only to discuss your expressed interest in our tours or your current booking. Your mailing address will be used only when sending invoices or information relevant to a tour you’ve reserved.Your email address is used to provide requested information about our tours, to communicate with current clients, or for our monthly e-newsletters.If you would like to opt out of email communication, you may unsubscribe at any time by clicking “Manage Your Subscription” at the bottom of each e-newsletter or by emailing us.If you would like to have your information permanently removed from our database, please email info@dolcetours.com.La Dolce Vita Wine Tours respects the legal provisions provided for by European law as regards to privacy and the treatment of personal data. For any further information, please contact La Dolce Vita Wine Tours Inc., 576 Fifth Street, Brooklyn, NY 11215.
REGIONSPiedmontVeneto/Alto AdigeLiguriaEmilia RomagnaTuscanyUmbriaCampaniaSicilyCOUNTRIESItalySpainPortugalINTERESTSWineWine IntensiveWalking & WineCustom WineCustom WalkCustom BikeGENERAL INFOPRIVACY POLICY© 2019 La Dolce Vita Wine Tours576 Fifth Street, Brooklyn NY 11215718-788-6365 info@dolcetours.com
